[ { "problem": "000000090400007062263050801007091206180005700090040083038009000000370504710020000", "solution": "871263495459187362263954871347891256182635749695742183538419627926378514714526938" },
{ "problem": "020000147500800000390706000078000009634009800200004013705018900000500620910003008", "solution": "826935147547821396391746285178352469634179852259684713765218934483597621912463578" },
{ "problem": "050040630008000010400063209020908150080000002003104000039005806710002394006700000", "solution": "952841637368297415471563289624978153187356942593124768239415876715682394846739521" },
{ "problem": "300009500702100008090080026020050014904008000560320070000500480030706002050041900", "solution": "386279541742165398195483726823957614974618235561324879619532487438796152257841963" },
{ "problem": "206800001840900020000032040052007060090406350103000000000070018001029604079008005", "solution": "236854791847961523915732846452387169798416352163295487524673918381529674679148235" },
{ "problem": "207030040019000805050600002708502069040008003092004100403079050800240016000000070", "solution": "287935641619427835354681792738512469146798523592364187463179258875243916921856374" },
{ "problem": "098065004023807100106430000000006839000200600070080050900043007264070900800001500", "solution": "798165324423897165156432798542716839389254671671389452915643287264578913837921546" },
{ "problem": "000000600694032700580040000020057000400000001036900008002503810071029034000080027", "solution": "217895643694132785583746192128357469459268371736914258942573816871629534365481927" },
{ "problem": "070608030160024000905100004000709340200005900006400078530000800008507001009006200", "solution": "472658139163924785985173624851769342247385916396412578534291867628537491719846253" },
{ "problem": "800050096003000204020907010100300700069100820000000040030004900500806002470290180", "solution": "817452396953681274624937518142368759769145823385729641238514967591876432476293185" },
{ "problem": "300057000000160049269003001030640000046009078028000030100800094000530600087000500", "solution": "314957862875162349269483751731648925546329178928715436153876294492531687687294513" } ]
